Today, we are launching Imagen 2.0. If
we think of DALL-E [music] as cave
drawings and Imagen 1 as ancient art,
then Imagen 2.0 is
the Renaissance.
>> [music]
>> Imagen 2.0 is the smartest image
generation model ever built with the
ability to generate complex, polished,
and production-ready visuals
>> [music]
>> with accurate text and structured
design. You see, this model isn't just
generating images.
It's thinking. That's right. Imagen 2.0
is thinking and [music] researching, and
it can even search the web to generate
images with the most accurate
information [music] available.
And with that information, the model is
able to generate infographics that
explain complex systems and images that
[music] solve math problems with proofs.
And with [music] new multilingual
capabilities, you can create visuals
with multiple languages for the entire
world.
And now, for the first time in image
generation, [music]
you can create multiple distinct images
at once. So, you can generate entire
magazines with structured typography and
photorealistic photos, full renovation
plans for every room in your house,
or manga comics with recurring
characters and evolving storylines.
And you can now generate images with 2K
resolution [music] across multiple
aspect ratios with extraordinary micro
details.
>> [music]
>> You see, we are no longer generating
images to marvel at. With Imagen 2.0,
we're generating [music] images to
discover and navigate, to invent and
build, to dream and explore the world,
and bring ideas
to life. Lights on.
>> [music]